the exact scenarios we train,
I hope they never use it.
What is something that the
public might be surprised
to learn about from astronaut
training for Artemis
missions?
I think the most surprising
thing is how little of
our training I want
them to use in flight.
That’s a good point.
Like we spend most of our time
training worst case
scenarios,
different failure things
that could go wrong,
and ideally nothing— Yeah.
Nothing off nominal
happens during the mission.
But by practicing all
of those failures,
they’re learning the process.
They’re working as a team.
There’s a lot of skills
that are applicable,
but the exact
scenarios we train,
I hope they never use it.